Guide to the Farm Bureau scrapbooks, New York State,1912-1934.
Farm Bureau scrapbooks, New York State,1912-1934.
- Series XVIII. 1934
  - Oswego County, 1934 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Otsego County, 1934 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Otsego County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Rensselaer County, 1934 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Rockland County, 1934 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Saratoga County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1934 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Schenectady County, 1934 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Schoharie County, 1934 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Seneca County, 1934 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Steuben County, 1934 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Suffolk County, 1934 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Sullivan County, 1934 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Tioga County, 1934 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Tompkins County, 1934 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Wyoming County, 1934 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Ulster County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Warren County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Washington County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Wayne County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Westchester County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Yates County, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 47)
- Series XIX. 1935
  - Allegany County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Albany County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Broome County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Cattaraugus County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Cayuga County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Chautauqua County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Chemung County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Chenango County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Clinton County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Columbia County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Cortland County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Cortland County, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Delaware County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Delaware County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Dutchess County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Erie County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Essex County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Franklin County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Fulton County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Genesee County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Greene County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Herkimer County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Jefferson County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Jefferson County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Livingston County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Madison County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Monroe County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Montgomery County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Nassau County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Niagara County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Oneida County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Onondaga County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Onondaga County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Ontario County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Orange County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Oswego County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Rensselaer County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Rockland County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Saratoga County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Schenectady County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Schoharie County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Seneca County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Seneca County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - St. Lawrence, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Steuben County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Suffolk County, 1935 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Sullivan County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Tioga County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Tioga County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Tompkins County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Tompkins County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Ulster County, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Warren County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Warren County, 1935 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Washington County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Washington County, 1935 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Westchester County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Westchester County, 1935 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Wyoming County, 1935 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Yates-Schuyler County, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 42)
- Series XX. 1936
  - Albany County, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Allegany County, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Broome County, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Cattaraugus County, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Cayuga County, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Chautauqua County, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Chemung County, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Chenango County, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Clinton County, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Columbia County, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Cortland County, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Delaware County, 1936 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Delaware County, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Dutchess County, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Erie County, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Essex County, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Franklin County, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Fulton County, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Genesee County, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Greene County, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Herkimer County, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Jefferson COunty, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Livingston County, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Nassau County, 1936-37 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Ontario County, 1936 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - Orange County, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Orleans County, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Warren County, 1936 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - Washington County, 1936 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Yates County, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Yates County, 1936 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Series XXI. 1937
  - Albany County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Allegany County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Broome County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Cattaraugus County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Cayuga County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Chautaugua County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Chemung County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Chenango County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Clinton County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Columbia County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Cortland County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Delaware County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Dutchess County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Erie County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Essex County, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Franklin County, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Fulton County, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Genessee County, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Greene County, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Herkimer County, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Jefferson County, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Lewis County, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Livingston County, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Madison County, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Monroe County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Montgomery County, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Nassau County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Niagara County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Oneida County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Onondaga County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Onondaga County, 1937 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Ontario County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Orange County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Oswego County, 1937 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Otsego County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Otsego County, 1937 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Rockland County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Saratoga County, 1937 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Schenectady County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Schoharie County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Schuyler County, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Seneca County, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Steuben County, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Suffolk County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Sullivan County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Tioga County, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Tompkins County, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Ulster County, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Warren County, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Washington County, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Westchester County, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Wyoming County, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Yates County, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Series XXII. 1938
  - Albany County, 1938 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Allegany County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Broome County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Cattaraugus County, 1938 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Cayuga County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Chemung County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Chenango County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - Clinton County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Columbia County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - Cortland County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Delaware County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Dutchess County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Erie County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Essex County, 1938 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Jefferson County, 1938 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Lewis County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Lewis County, 1938 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Livingston County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Madison County, 1938 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Monroe County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Monroe County, 1938 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Montgomery County, 1938 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Nassau County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Niagara, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Onondaga County, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Ontario County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Orange County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Orleans County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Oswego County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Otsego County, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Rensselaer County, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Rockland County, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Saratoga County, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Schoharie County, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Schuyler County, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Seneca County, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Steuben County, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Suffolk County, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Suffok County, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Sullivan County, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Tioga County, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Tompkins County, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Ulster County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Warren County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Washington County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Wayne County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Westchester County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Wyoming County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Yates County, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 24)
- Series XXIII. 1939
  - Albany County, 1939 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Allegany County, 1939 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Broome County, 1939 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Cattaraugus County, 1939 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Cayuga County, 1939 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Chautauqua County, 1939 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Chemung County, 1939 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Chenango County, 1939 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Clinton County, 1939 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Columbia County, 1939 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Cortland County, 1939 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Delaware County, 1939 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Dutchess County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Dutchess County, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Erie County, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Essex County, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Franklin County, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Fulton County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Fulton County, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Genesee County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Genesee County, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Greene County, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Herkimer County, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Jefferson County, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Lewis County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Livingston County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Madison County, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Monroe County, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Montgomery County, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Nassau County, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Niagara County, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Oneida County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Onondaga County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Ontario County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Orange County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Orleans County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Oswego County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Otsego County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Rensselaer County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Rockland County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Saratoga County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Schenectady County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Schoharie County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Schuyler County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Seneca County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Steuben County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Suffolk County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Sullivan County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Tioga County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Tompkins County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Ulster County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Wayne County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Washington County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Warren County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Westchester County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Wyoming County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Yates County, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Series XXIV. Constitutions and Bylaws
  - Constitutions and Bylaws-County Farm and Home Bureau Associations, A-N, 1917-1922 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Constitutions and Bylaws-County Farm and Home Bureau Associations, O-V, 1917-1922 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Series XXV. Memorandums
  - Central Farm Bureau, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Memorandums on Appointments, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - F.B. Holmes- Director (Employees' Retirement System), 1930 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Memorandums on Apointments, 1930 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Memoramdums to Wheeler-Ladd-Parker (Retirement), 1930 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Mr. William Johnson (Employees' Retirement System), 1930 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Table of Contents, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence Regarding Salaries, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Memorandums on Appointments, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - U.S.D.A. Payrolls, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Series XXVI. Committee Meetings
  - NYS Farm Debt Conciliation Committee, 1934 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Corn-Hog: Educational Meetings, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Corn-Hog State Board of Review (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Referendum: Corn-Hog, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Corn-Hog: Correspondence, Mr. Del De Haan, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Corn-Hog: Forms, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Series XXVII. Correspondence
  - Circulars - Ours, Corn Hog, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Corn-Hog General Correspondence, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Corn-Hog General Correspondence, A.W. True, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - General Correspondence, C.R. Wickard, CH, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Letters to L.R. Simons on Appt. + Redistribution, 1940-1941 (Box 38, Folder 51)
  - Comproller's Office, 1918-1919 (Box 49, Folder 49-5)
  - Concerning State Dept. Education, 1919 (Box 49, Folder 49-6)
  - Concerning appointments of agents, 1919 (Box 49, Folder 49-7)
  - Bureau of Animal Industry, 1918 (Box 49, Folder 49-8)
  - Concerning Crop Estimates, 1918-1919 (Box 49, Folder 49-9)
  - Benson, O.H., 1918-1919 (Box 49, Folder 49-10)
  - L.A. Clinton, 1918 (Box 49, Folder 49-11)
  - C.E. Ladd, 1918-1919 (Box 49, Folder 49-12)
  - W.A. Lloyd, 1918 (Box 49, Folder 49-13)
  - Porter, Eugene, 1918-1919 (Box 49, Folder 49-14)
  - Ws (Box 49, Folder 49-15)
  - Florence Ward, 1918-1919 (Box 49, Folder 49-16)
  - C.R. White, 1918 (Box 49, Folder 49-17)
  - C.S. Wilson, 1918-1919 (Box 49, Folder 49-18)
  - Wing H.H., 1918-1919 (Box 49, Folder 49-19)
  - Winters, Harry, 1918-1919 (Box 49, Folder 49-20)
  - D.W. Working, 1918 (Box 49, Folder 49-21)
  - G.A. Works, 1918-1919 (Box 49, Folder 49-22)
  - Women's Land Army Corp- Mrs. Otto Eichel, Director, 1918-1919 (Box 49, Folder 49-23)
  - Wright, W.J. - Rural Education, 1919 (Box 49, Folder 49-24)
  - YWCA, 1918 (Box 49, Folder 49-25)
- Series XXVIII. Flood and Drought Relief, Flood Relief
  - NYS Flood Relief, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Flood Relief, Mississippi Valley, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Drought Relief, New York, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Drought Relief, NYS, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 29)
- Series XXIX. Land Use Project
  - Land Use Project-Annual and Semi-annual Reports, 1940-1942 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Land Use, 1938-1939 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - L.U.P. Misc. Information, 1939-1941 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Land Use Project-Monthly Reports, 1939-1941 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - U.S.D.A.-B.A.E. Land Use Project Work Outlines, 1939-1940 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Land Use Farming State Committee, 1940-1941 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - U.S.D.A.-B.A.E. Land Use Project Unified Programs, 1941 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Land Use Planning Agreement, 1940-1942 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - State Land Use Comm. Meeting Minutes, 1940-1941 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - U.S.D.A.-B.A.E. Land Use Project, General, 1939-1941 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Report-Land Use Program, B.A.E. Representative, July 1st-Dec. 31st, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - State Land Use Committee Meetings Minutes, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Tours, 1940 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Farm Forestry Plan, NYS, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Farm Adjustments, 1941 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Farm Forestry, 1940-1942 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Maintaining Soil Fertility, no date available (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Marketing and Distribution, 1940-1942 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Rural Social Resources, 1940-1941 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Soil Conservation, Flood Control, and Drainage, 1940-1941 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Taxation, Government, Rural Zoning, 1940 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Uses of Land Classes I and II, 1941 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Land Use, 1938-1945 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - Land Use Planning, 1939-1941 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence on Land Use Suggestions, 1939-1945 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - Committee for Economic Development, 1939-1944 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Post-War Agriculture, 1944 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Post-War Planning, 1944 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - County Bibliography-NYS College of Agriculture, 1937 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Unified Land Use Program, 1939 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Wyoming County Conference Committee, 1937 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Genesee County Agricultural Conference Committee, 1937 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Series XXX. Extension Files
  - Albany Land Use Committee, 1939-1940 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Allegany County Rural Policy Committee, 1939-1945 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Cattaraugus County LUP Committee, 1939-1941 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Cayuga County Agricultural Land Use Committee, 1939-1942 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Chautauqua County Conference, 1939-1941 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Chenango County Agricultural LUP Committee, 1941-1942 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Cortland County Agricultural LUP Committee Tour, 1939-1941 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Delaware County Agricultural LUP Committee Soils Tour, 1937-1942 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Dutchess County Land Use Committee, 1938-1939 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Erie County Rural Policy Committee Meeting, 1939-1945 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Essex County Agricultural LUP Committee, 1940-1941 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Fulton County Agricultural Land Use Committee, 1940-1941 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Genesee County Land Use Committee, 1938-1939 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Herkimer County Land Use Planning Committee, 1940-1941 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Jefferson County Agricultural LUP Committee, 1934-1944 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Lewis County LUP Committee, 1934-1941 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Livingston County Agricultural LUP Committee, 1938-1942 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Madison County Agricultural LUP Committee, 1940-1941 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Monroe County Agricultural LUP Committee, 1935-1942 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Montgomery County Agricultural LUP Committee, 1935-1942 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Niagara County Agricultural LUP Committee, 1938-1940 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Oneida County LUP Committee, 1938-1939 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Onondaga County Agricultural LUP Committee, 1940-1942 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Ontario County Agricultural LUP Committee, 1940-1942 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Orange County Land Use Committee, 1940 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Orleans County Agricultural LUP Committee, 1940-1944 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Oswego County Land Use Committee, 1938-1939 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Otsego County Land Use Committee, 1939-1941 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Rensselaer County Agricultural LUP Committee, 1938-1940 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Rockland County Land Use Committee, 1939-1945 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - St. Lawrence County Agricultural LUP Committee, 1934-1940 (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Schenectady County Agricultural LUP Committee, 1938-1945 (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Schoharie County Rural Policy Committee, 1938-1945 (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - Schuyler County Land Use Committee, 1939-1941 (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - Seneca County Agricultural LUP Committee, 1939-1942 (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - Steuben County Land Use Committee, 1938-1939 (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - Sullivan County Land Use Committee, 1939-1940 (Box 38, Folder 45)
  - Tioga County Rural Policy Commitee, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 46)
  - Washington County Rural Policy Committee, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 47)
  - Wayne County Land Use Committee, 1938-1940 (Box 38, Folder 48)
  - Wyoming County Agricultural LUP Committee, 1938-1942 (Box 38, Folder 49)
  - Yates County Land Use Committee, 1938-1940 (Box 38, Folder 50)
- Series XXXI. Soil Conservation Districts
  - Albany County Soil Conservation District, 1945-1950 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Allegany County Soil Conservation District, 1946-1949 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Broome County Soil Conservation District, 1944-1950 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Cattaraugus County Soil Conservation District, 1945-1947 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Cayuga County Soil Conservation District, 1947-1950 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Chautauqua County Soil Conservation District, 1946-1959 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Chenango County Soil Conservation District, 1940-1949 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Cortland County Soil Conservation District, 1946-1950 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Delaware County Soil Conservation District, 1946-1949 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Dutchess County Soil Conservation District, 1946-1950 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Erie County Soil Conservation District, 1946-1949 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Fulton County Soil Conservation District, 1946-1950 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Genesee County Soil Conservation District, 1944-1949 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Lewis County Soil Conservation District, 1947-1950 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Livingston County Soil Conservation District, 1946-1950 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Madison County Soil Conservation District, 1947-1949 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - Montgomery County Soil Conservation District, 1947-1950 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - Oneida County Soil Conservation District, 1946-1950 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - Onondaga County Soil Conservation District, 1944-1948 (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - Ontario County Soil Conservation District, 1946-1948 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - Orleans County Soil Conservation District, 1946-1949 (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - Oswego County Soil Conservation District, 1945-1947 (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Otsego County Soil Conservation District, 1944-1948 (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - Saratoga County Soil Conservation District, 1947-1949 (Box 39, Folder 45)
  - Seneca County Soil Conservation District, 1946-1949 (Box 39, Folder 46)
  - Schenectady County Soil Conservation District, 1946-1950 (Box 39, Folder 47)
  - Schoharie County Soil Conservation District, 1946-1949 (Box 39, Folder 48)
  - Schuyler County Soil Conservation District, 1946-1950 (Box 39, Folder 49)
  - Steuben County Soil Conservation District, 1946-1949 (Box 39, Folder 50)
  - Tioga County Soil Conservation District, 1947-1949 (Box 39, Folder 51)
  - Tompkins County Soil Conservation District, 1946-1948 (Box 39, Folder 52)
  - Washington County Soil Conservation District, 1946-1949 (Box 39, Folder 53)
  - Wayne County Soil Conservation District, 1948-1949 (Box 39, Folder 54)
  - Wyoming County Soil Conservation District, 1946-1949 (Box 39, Folder 55)
  - Yates County Soil Conservation District, 1946-1950 (Box 39, Folder 56)
- Series XXXII. 1952
  - Albany, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Allegany County, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Broome County, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Cattaraugus County, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Cayuga County, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Chautauqua County, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Chemung County, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 11)